

CONTACT INFO

• Cengkareng, Jakarta Barat

0812-8176-8727

tiasafernanda@gmail.com

in Tiasa Fernanda Muhamad Putra

SKILLS SUMMARY

● ● ● ● Microsoft Office

•••• Zendesk

••• English

• • • ● Photography & Videography

VOLUNTEER & ORGANIZATION EXPERIENCE

- Staff Infomedia at Himpunan Mahasiswa Perikanan (2014 -2015)
- Volunteer at Konferensi Asia
 Afrika (2015)
- Head of Entrepreneurship
 Division at Himpunan
 Perikanan (2015 2016)
- Administration Staff for PON & PEPARNAS West Java (2016)

TIASA FERNANDA MUHAMAD PUTRA

OPERATION ANALYST

PERSONAL PROFILE

A confident, reliable and enthusiastic individual, with previous customer service experience at one of Indonesia's Unicorn Start Up. I enjoy helping customers and solving any problems that they may have. I am a great communicator, over the phone and via email. Also, passionate about social media activity and comfortable with any different working shifts.

WORK EXPERIENCE

VVIP TEAM - CRISIS CENTER

PT Bukalapak.com Tbk | AUG 2020 - JUL 2021

- Resolve customer hard complaints via phone and email
- Identify and assess customers' needs to achieve satisfaction about payments, logistics, bugs and fraud issues
- Analyze customer experience reports and insights and come up with improvement suggestions and initiatives

SOCIAL MEDIA SUPPORT

PT Bukalapak.com Tbk | AUG 2018 - JUL 2020

- Handle customer inquiries about Bukalapak product's through social media
- Manage and resolve customer related issues
- Be the voice of customers to provide feedback to the company

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

 2012 - 2017 Padjadjaran University, Faculty of Fisheries and Marine Science, Major of Fisheries (GPA Scale: 3.13 from 4.00)

• 2009 - 2012 Senior High School 78 Jakarta

• 2006 - 2009 Junior High School 45 Jakarta